http://www.pelagicgear.com/pages/privacy-policy

${ minicartMessage }
${ item.title } - ${ item.size.value } is Sold Out. Please remove from cart.
Only ${ item.inventory_quantity - inventoryThreshold } left. Please adjust amount in cart.
Size: ${ item.size.value }
Quantity:
Quantity
${ item.quantity }
Price:
Or Buy With
Your cart is currently empty.
Overview
Pelagic Inc. ("Pelagic," "we," "us," or "our) values its relationship with you, and your privacy is important to us. Below we describe personal information that we may receive in connection with your use of Pelagic's Services, how and why we receive it, your rights and options, and the efforts we make to safeguard it all. When you provide personal information to Pelagic, you agree to provide only true, accurate, current, and complete information.
What this policy covers
This Privacy Policy covers Pelagic's processing as data controller of your personal information, including information we receive when you use Pelagic's Services or share information with any of Pelagic's third party partners. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with this policy and contact us if you have any questions.This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Pelagic does not own or control, or to individuals whom Pelagic does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties from which Pelagic may obtain or to which Pelagic may disclose user personal information as set forth in this policy. The practices of such third parties are governed by their respective privacy policies.
Policy Changes
This policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided to you about our privacy practices. We reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. Any changes to this policy will become effective upon posting of the revised policy on Pelagic’s Website. If there are material changes to this policy or our privacy practices, we will notify you prior to their becoming effective, and we will seek your consent where required.
How information we receive about you
We receive information about you when you visit our Websites and/or use our Services. This information includes certain personal information (information that can be used to personally identify you, either directly or indirectly) and certain non-personal information (information that does not permit a direct association with you). In some cases, we may ask you to provide identifying information, such as your name and contact information, in order to access certain Services. We request personal information as is necessary to fulfill our contractual obligations to you and for the limited business purposes identified below. Your disclosure of this information is voluntary. However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may be unable to access these Services.Personal information may be obtained either directly by Pelagic or indirectly through its third party partners. Please note that we process the following personal information: your first name, last name, date of birth, gender, billing address(es), shipping address(es), e-mail address(es), telephone number(s), payment information (payment method; credit card, debit card, gift card, rewards program, and coupon code information; and “Bill To” address), location information (continent, country, region, state or province, zip code, city, store vicinity, and “Ship To” address), order and purchase history, search queries, product and service preferences, account information (including but not limited to username(s), password(s), and settings), as well as connection, log and browsing data, the device(s) you use to access our Services, operating system, device information, unique device identifiers, IP address, referring site/application, app version, visit metrics, action metrics, page view metrics, and search metrics.
How we use the information we receive
We may process your personal information for the following purposes as a result of the contractual or pre-contractual relationships between you and us:
to process your online shopping on our Services, including
to implement transactions and to maintain details of your order history;
to contact you and provide you with the products, services, information and/or assistance you request;
to manage your electronic and catalog subscriptions;
to manage your participation in sweepstakes, games, and contests in which you have chosen to participate; and
to address your claims resulting from the performance of agreements between you and us.
Moreover, subject to your express prior consent, we also may process your personal information for the following purposes:
to provide you with suggestions and information in which you may be interested;
to make and display advertisements and to measure or understand the effectiveness thereof (including but not limited to targeted advertisements); and
for implementing business analysis.
You may withdraw your consent at any time. Please note that withdrawing consent will affect the processing of your information going forward but will not affect the legality of our processing of your information prior to the withdrawal. To exercise your right of withdrawal, refer to the Opting Out section below.We also may collect and process your personal information for the purposes identified below, which are required in order for us to pursue our legitimate interest:
to ensure that the information and content available on our Services is presented in an effective manner;
to improve the clothes we design and/or manufacture, so as to better meet market expectations, and to improve our online platform so that it is easier to use;
to protect the integrity and operation of our Services, and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research and service improvement;
to make you aware of any changes to our Services;
to bring legal action to protect your safety or rights or the safety or rights of Pelagic or others; and
to comply with requests from authorized law enforcement authorities.
How long we keep your information
We keep personal information up to 5 years following a customer's latest contact with us.
How do we protect your personal information
Protecting your personal information is important to us. We use industry standard technology to protect the security of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us.
Making purchases
We guarantee you will only pay for authorized items that you have ordered.You will have the option of saving certain information, including your personal information, in our system for your convenience with respect to future purchases. The information is stored in the form of a “cookie” in your computer (for additional information regarding cookies, please see below). Even though you need cookies to be enabled to make an online purchase, it is not necessary to save information via cookies if you choose not to.By registering an account with Pelagic, your checkout will be quicker and more efficient, with easy access to your order history, shipping preferences, wish lists, and special offers. If you're not comfortable shopping online and wish to phone in your order, you are welcome to do so.
Electronic subscriptions
If you sign up for our electronic and catalog subscriptions, you'll be the first to hear about upcoming sales, online exclusive discounts, contests and more. For example, you can sign up to receive our Pelagic email newsletter during check-out and in various locations of the Services.You'll always be able to unsubscribe from these electronic subscriptions, and we have a Contact Preference Center where you can manage these subscriptions so you only get what you're interested in or contact us.
Online contests and sweepstakes
We're always creating new, fun online contests and sweepstakes at Pelagic. Most sweepstakes and contests are open to U.S. residents age 13 and older, If you are over this age, but under the age of majority in your state, make sure you get your parent’s permission before entering any personal info.To enter a given sweepstakes or contest, you may need to provide certain information to us, including personal information. If you are one of our winners, we'll use this information to contact you. Contest sponsors may utilize your info based on which opt-in(s) you have selected on the sweepstakes or contest entry pages.
Cookies and other tracking technologies
Cookies are data files saved to your computer’s hard drive when you visit a site. A “session cookie” expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A “persistent cookie” stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still availableWe use session and persistent cookies, either directly or through a third party partner, as well as along other tracking technologies (including but not limited to pixel tags and web beacons). These cookies enable us to operate our Services as you have requested, and facilitate your browsing and the use of our Services, so that you enjoy a seamless experience (e.g., we will remember which is your preferred language and will display the content of our Services accordingly). Please note that we use cookies to carry out traffic and business analytics as well as statistics activities, which enable us to understand how you use our Services and improve them, as well as to provide you with targeted advertising.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent and decide if you are willing to accept it or not, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. However, if you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient, and some of our Services will not function properly.If you consent to our use of cookies but later wish to opt out, you may do so at any time through your browser settings, which allow you to delete the cookies that have been set and change your browser settings to block all or part of any further cookies.
Cookie Settings
Disclosure to third parties
Pelagic relies on third-party vendors and service providers to provide support and assistance for our Services and products. We may share your personal information with such third parties in order to help us conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products and services. We may contract with various third-party service providers in furtherance of this goal, including but not limited to payment processors, website hosting partners, banks, cookie providers, and others.We also work with third-party advertising, marketing and analytics partners to serve ads on this or other sites, using information collected through the use of industry standard technologies such as cookies and pixel tags. These third parties may receive information about you over time and across different websites when you use our Services. Our corporate affiliates also may receive your personal information when you use our Services.If Pelagic is sold to or merges with another company, or declares bankruptcy, some or all of the personal information collected about you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets, subject only to agreement by the acquirer that the personal information will be subject to the same or substantially similar privacy protections as those established by this Privacy Policy.Pelagic collaborates with government agencies and security organizations to prevent fraud and fraudulent use of your information, including your personal information. During fraud prevention investigations, we may share information, including your personal information, with the agencies that assist us, as permitted and required by U.S. law.Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with third parties unless we have received your permission, given you notice (such as by telling you about it in this Privacy Policy), or irreversibly removed any information from which you could be identified, directly or indirectly. Where we share your personal information with service providers or any other third parties who perform services on our behalf, except as otherwise provided herein, they will be contractually restricted from using your information in any manner other than in helping us conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products and services.We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose, including providing it to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Your rights
You are entitled to access the personal information we keep about you, ask for the modification of such information, and receive such information in a structured and standard format. You also may ask us to erase your personal information or restrict us from processing it. You have the right to object to processing of your personal information. To exercise such rights, please refer to the Contact Us section below. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a local regulatory authority about how your personal information has been processed.
Your California privacy rights
If you are a California resident, California law permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Pelagic does not disclose your personal information for third parties’ direct marketing purposes.California law also permits minors to request and obtain deletion of certain posted content. For additional information or to make such a request, please contact us.
Children
Our Services are not directed to persons under age 13 in the U.S., or the equivalent age in other jurisdictions (such as 16 in the EU). Users must be at least this age to access, use, or register for the Services. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from persons under this age without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a user under this age without first receiving verifiable parental consent, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.If you are a parent and you think we have inadvertently collected personal information from your child who is under this age, you may contact us to request instructions on how to delete this content from the Services.
Optin-out, removing or modifying your information
We offer several ways for you to update your information that is obtained and stored by Pelagic, including options to change your account preferences and remove your email from e-mail updates:
To unsubscribe from electronic updates, please visit the Contact Preference Center
You may also contact us.
Contact us
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
1660 Placentia AvenueCosta Mesa, CA 92627(949) 265-7870
Email us or visit our Contact page
